export const questions = [
  {
    questionText: 'What is by far the most utilized punch in boxing?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'The cross',
      'b': 'The hook',
      'c': 'The jab'
    },
    correctAnswer: 'c',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'When does a boxer become undisputed champion in his/her weightclass?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'When she/he has aquired 50 wins in their respective weightclass',
      'b': 'When she/he has aquired the IBF, WBO, WBA and WBC belts',
      'c': 'When she/he has aquired the IBF, WBO, WBA, WBC and WTT belts',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'What did former boxing champion Vasyl Lomatjenkos dad make him do for 4 years before he could start training boxing?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'Ukranian folk dance, to give him an advantage in his footwork',
      'b': 'Swimming, to give him an advantage in back strength, core strength and endurance',
      'c': 'Wrestling, to give him an advantage in overall strength and mental prowess',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'Which one of these boxers were heavyweight champion of the world at one point in their career?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'Jimmy Young',
      'b': 'Michael Bentt',
      'c': 'Ron Lyle',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'What preferred offense does a "Muay khao" fighter use?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'His/her knees',
      'b': 'His/her hands',
      'c': 'His/her elbows',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'Who is the only muay thaiboxer who has won "Sports Writers of Thailand Fighter of the Year" three years in a row?',
    answerOptions:{ 
      'a': 'Samart Payakaroon, 1981 - 1983',
      'b': 'Petchboonchu FA Group, 2006 - 2008',
      'c': 'Panpayak Jitmuangnon, 2013 - 2015',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'c',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'What stadium in Thailand is historically held with the highest regard when it comes to professional muay thai?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'Rajadamnern stadium in Bangkok',
      'b': 'Bangla stadium in Phuket',
      'c': 'Rawai stadium in Rawai',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'What is a "Wai khru ram muay" and what does it represent?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'An armband which is worn throughout the fight which honors your respective gym and khru (trainer)',
      'b': 'A fighters last fight which is often more of a showing/spectacle combined with a speech to honor said fighters journey, krhus (trainers), gym and fans',
      'c': 'A ritualistic dance which is performed before a fight to show respect and gratitude to the parents, khrus (trainers), ancestors and the ring itself',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'c',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'What was the first weightclass that irish MMA fighter Conor McGregor became champion of while in the UFC?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'Featherweight',
      'b': 'Welterweight',
      'c': 'Lightweight',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'Several high ranked MMA fighters and champions descend from which well-known wrestling-heavy russian republic?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'The Chechen Republic',
      'b': 'The Republic of Dagestan',
      'c': 'The Republic of Mordovia',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'b',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'Besides the UFC, name one other well-known MMA organisation around the world',
    answerOptions : {
      'a': 'Tukhgul MMA Championship',
      'b': 'GSP Fighting Championship',
      'c': 'Bellator MMA',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'c',
  },
  {
    questionText: 'Which MMA fighter/champion has held the longest winningstreak ever in the UFC?',
    answerOptions: {
      'a': 'Anderson Silva, middleweight, light heavyweight: 2006 - 2013',
      'b': 'Tony Ferguson, lightweight: 2013 - 2020',
      'c': 'Demetrious Johnson, flyweight: 2012 - 2018',
    },
    correctAnswer: 'a',
  },
];